(this["webpackJsonpreact-lap"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-lap"]||[]).push([[0],{32:function(e,s,t){},41:function(e,s,t){"use strict";t.r(s);var n=t(18),o=t(19),r=t(28),i=t(26),a=t(1),c=t.n(a),u=(t(32),t(20)),d=t.n(u),l=[{question:" What does Dozen mean? ",answers:["11","12","13","14"],correct:"12",questionId:"1"},{question:"What country is Sushi from?",answers:["Wales","Moldova","Japan","Denmark"],correct:"Japan",questionId:"2"},{question:"How long is A Fortnight?",answers:["One week","One month","27 days","Two weeks"],correct:"Two weeks",questionId:"3"},{question:"How long is the lifespan of an average housefly?",answers:["28 days","26 days","27 days","29 days"],correct:"28 days",questionId:"4"},{question:"When Michael Jordan played for the Chicago Bulls, how many NBA Championships did he win?",answers:["8","5","6","7"],correct:"6",questionId:"5"},{question:"How many days are in a year?",answers:["364","367","366","365"],correct:"365",questionId:"10"},{question:"According to the Old Testament, how many days did it take God to create the world??",answers:["6","5","4","7"],correct:"6",questionId:"11"},{question:"How many different kinds of chemical bonds are there?",answers:["3","4","2","5"],correct:"3",questionId:"13"},{question:"How many soccer players should each team have on the field at the start of each match?",answers:["10","11","9","12"],correct:"11",questionId:"14"},{question:"How many countries still have the shilling as currency?",answers:["3","6","4","5"],correct:"4",questionId:"15"},{question:"What is the square root of 144?",answers:["11","10","13","12"],correct:"12",questionId:"16"},{question:"How many of Henry VIII\u2019s wives were called Catherine?",answers:["2","3","5","4"],correct:"3",questionId:"17"},{question:"In what US State is the city Nashville?",answers:["Nevada","Arizona","Tennessee","Utah"],correct:"Tennessee",questionId:"26"},{question:"How many times has Andy Murray won Wimbledon playing singles?",answers:["0"," 3","2","1"],correct:"2",questionId:"18"},{question:"Who owns Google.com?",answers:["Number","Letter","Sign","Alphabet"],correct:"Alphabet",questionId:"19"},{question:"Which is the world's most populous country?",answers:["India","China","Brazil","America"],correct:"China",questionId:"20"},{question:"How Long Should You Boil A Hard-Boiled Egg?",answers:["19","20","12","15"],correct:"12",questionId:"12"},{question:"A Broken Clock Is Still Right ___ A Day?",answers:["thrice","once","twice","four times"],correct:"twice",questionId:"21"},{question:"How many World Wars did Switzerland take part in?",answers:["3","2","1","0"],correct:"0",questionId:"22"},{question:"What year was the very first model of the iPhone released?",answers:["2007","2008","2006","2005"],correct:"2007",questionId:"23"},{question:"Which is the only vowel not used as the first letter in a US State?",answers:["I","E","A","O"],correct:"E",questionId:"24"},{question:"At what temperature Fahrenheit does water boil?",answers:["211","210","212","213"],correct:"212",questionId:"25"},{question:"What year was Heinz established?",answers:["1871","1870","1868","1869"],correct:"1869",questionId:"27"},{question:"What's the biggest animal in the world??",answers:["The blue whale","Tiger","Panda","Crocodile"],correct:"The blue whale",questionId:"9"},{question:" How many countries are in the world?",answers:["195","194","193","196"],correct:"195",questionId:"28"},{question:"What is the nickname of the US state of Florida?",answers:["Golden State","Sunshine State","Bay State","Treasure State"],correct:"Sunshine State",questionId:"30"},{question:"About what percentage of the earth's surface is water?",answers:["80","60","70","90"],correct:"70",questionId:"29"},{question:"What Insects Can Chew Through Wood And Destroy Your Home?",answers:["Larvae","Beetles","Termites","Ants"],correct:"Termites",questionId:"31"},{question:"How many players are there in a rugby league team?",answers:["12","14","11","13"],correct:"13",questionId:"50"},{question:"How many wonders of the ancient world are there?",answers:["5","8"," 6","7"],correct:"7",questionId:"32"},{question:" How many countries are in Africa??",answers:["100","54","25","68"],correct:"54",questionId:"37"},{question:"What\u2019s the shortcut for the \u201ccopy\u201d function on most computers?",answers:["ctrl c","ctrl a","ctrl d","ctrl b"],correct:"ctrl c",questionId:"33"},{question:"In which year was Joan of Arc burned at the stake?",answers:["1433","1431","1432","1430"],correct:"1431",questionId:"34"},{question:"How many branches are in the U.S. government?",answers:["2","5","3","4"],correct:"3",questionId:"35"},{question:"What year did Margaret Thatcher die?",answers:["2014","2012","2011","2013"],correct:"2013",questionId:"36"},{question:"How many moons does the earth have?",answers:["1","0","2","3"],correct:"1",questionId:"38"},{question:"How Many Days Are In February During A Leap Year",answers:["27","29","30","28"],correct:"29",questionId:"40"},{question:"When was Earth formed?",answers:["3.5 billion years ago","2.5 billion years ago","4.5 billion years ago","5.5 billion years ago"],correct:"4.5 billion years ago",questionId:"41"},{question:"Which planet is the hottest in the solar system?",answers:["Earth","Jupiter","Venus","Mars"],correct:"Venus",questionId:"42"},{question:"Which isn't a colour of the olympic ring?",answers:["Green","Red","Blue","Orange"],correct:"Orange",questionId:"43"},{question:"How many films have Al Pacino and Robert De Niro appeared in together?",answers:["2","1","4","3"],correct:"4",questionId:"44"},{question:"Which planet is closest to the sun?",answers:["Earth","Mars","Jupiter","Mercury"],correct:"Mercury",questionId:"45"},{question:"How many valves does the heart have?",answers:["5","3","6","4"],correct:"4",questionId:"46"},{question:"How many countries are in Europe?",answers:["44","42","45","43"],correct:"44",questionId:"47"},{question:"Which of these is not a major world ocean?",answers:["Pacific","Indian","American","Artic"],correct:"American",questionId:"39"},{question:"Prunes Were Once Which Kind Of Fruit?",answers:["Plums","Apricots","Pears","Figs"],correct:"Plums",questionId:"48"},{question:"Which planet has the most gravity?",answers:["Mecury","Saturn","Jupiter","Mars"],correct:"Jupiter",questionId:"49"},{question:"What is the smallest country in the world?",answers:["Brazil","China","South Korea","Vatican city"],correct:"Vatican city",questionId:"6"},{question:"The Great Lakes lie along the Canada/US border. How many are they?",answers:["5","3","4","6"],correct:"5",questionId:"7"},{question:"Where would you find the cruciate ligament?",answers:["Head","Shoulder","Knees","Toe"],correct:"Knees",questionId:"8"}],h=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return Promise.resolve(l.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},q=[{question:"Meteorology is the study of?",answers:["atmosphere","winds and clouds","air and sounds","seasons"],correct:"atmosphere",questionId:"31"},{question:"White light passing through a prism splits into?",answers:["8","5","6","7"],correct:"7",questionId:"15"},{question:"Primary colours of Light?",answers:["Red, Green, Blue","Red, Orange, Blue","White, Black, Blue","Red, Yellow, Blue"],correct:"Red, Green, Blue",questionId:"32"},{question:"Primary colours of pigments?",answers:["Red, Green, Blue","Red, Orange, Blue","White, Black, Blue","Red, Yellow, Blue"],correct:"Red, Yellow, Blue",questionId:"33"},{question:"Diamond is a form of?",answers:["Carbon","Hydrogen","Oxygen","Silicon"],correct:"Carbon",questionId:"34"},{question:"1 nanometer= ?",answers:["10-6m","10-6m","10-9m","10-12"],correct:"10-9m",questionId:"16"},{question:"SI unit of Heat?",answers:["Coulomb","Ohm","Volt","Joule"],correct:"Joule",questionId:"35"},{question:"Good sources of Vitamin-A?",answers:["green leafy vegetables","fresh vegetables and fruits","seeds","sea foods"],correct:"green leafy vegetables",questionId:"36"},{question:"Good sources of Vitamin-B complex?",answers:["green leafy vegetables","fresh vegetables and fruits","seeds","sea foods"],correct:"seeds",questionId:"37"},{question:"Good sources of Vitamin-C?",answers:["green leafy vegetables","fresh vegetables and fruits","seeds","sea foods"],correct:"fresh vegetables and fruits",questionId:"38"},{question:"Good sources of iodine?",answers:["green leafy vegetables","fresh vegetables and fruits","seeds","sea foods"],correct:"sea foods",questionId:"39"},{question:'What gas is called "laughing gas"?',answers:["Sodium Oxide","Carbon Dioxide","Sulfur Dioxide","Nitrous Oxide"],correct:"Nitrous Oxide",questionId:"40"},{question:"What is GPS?",answers:["Global Position Structure","Global Positioning System","Global PolySiliconium Store","Global Poles Systember"],correct:"Global Positioning System",questionId:"19"},{question:"What is oxidation?",answers:["Loss of Electrons","Gain of Protons","Loss of Protons","Gain of Electrons"],correct:"Loss of Electrons",questionId:"20"},{question:"Where is urine produced?",answers:["Liver","Kidneys","Lungs","Large intestine"],correct:"Kidneys",questionId:"21"},{question:"Blood is cleaned by?",answers:["Liver","Kidneys","Lungs","Large intestine"],correct:"Kidneys",questionId:"22"},{question:"The energy value of food is measured in ____?",answers:["Calories","Joule","Tesla","Proteins"],correct:"Calories",questionId:"41"},{question:"Wind energy is a _____ energy?",answers:["Potential","Mechanical","Kinetic","Transverse"],correct:"Kinetic",questionId:"42"},{question:"Who is considered the founder of meteorology?",answers:["Einstein","Aristotle","Plato","Newton"],correct:"Aristotle",questionId:"43"},{question:"The fourth state of matter is?",answers:["Water","Salts","Plasma","Vapours"],correct:"Plasma",questionId:"44"},{question:"Copper can be converted into gold by?",answers:["heating","Artificial radioactivity","Chemical reaction","Electroplating"],correct:"Artificial radioactivity",questionId:"45"},{question:"Bronze medal is made up of?",answers:["copper, silver","copper, zinc","copper,nickel","copper, tin"],correct:"copper, tin",questionId:"46"},{question:" Humming birds are?",answers:["Ectotherms","Endotherms","Exotherms","Heterotherms"],correct:"Endotherms",questionId:"47"},{question:"Isotope of Uranium in Nuclear Bomb?",answers:["92 U 234","92 U 238","92 U 235","92 U 233"],correct:"92 U 235",questionId:"48"},{question:"Percentage of water in milk?",answers:["80","60","70","90"],correct:"80",questionId:"3"},{question:"SI unit of charge?",answers:["Coulomb","Ohm","Volt","Ampere"],correct:"Coulomb",questionId:"4"},{question:"Very High Frequency have ____ wavelengths?",answers:["longest","longer","shortest","shorter"],correct:"shorter",questionId:"5"},{question:"Deficiency of Vitamin-A results in?",answers:["scurvy","rickets","Night blindness","hair fall"],correct:"Night blindness",questionId:"6"},{question:" The Lifespan of Red Blood Cells is ____ days?",answers:["100","120","25","68"],correct:"120",questionId:"7"},{question:"SI unit of pressure?",answers:["Coulomb","Ohm","Pascal","Ampere"],correct:"Pascal",questionId:"14"},{question:"Percentage of alcohol in spirit?",answers:["80","60","70","95"],correct:"95",questionId:"49"},{question:"Least abundant element in the Earth's crust?",answers:["Carbon Dioxide","Radium","Oxygen","Silicon"],correct:"Radium",questionId:"50"},{question:"A light year is a unit of?",answers:["Energy","Time","Length","Mass"],correct:"Length",questionId:"24"},{question:"Density of water?",answers:["1g/cm3","4g/cm3","2g/cm3","3g/cm3"],correct:"1g/cm3",questionId:"8"},{question:"Who discovered radioactivity?",answers:["Bacquerel","Kelvin","Rutherford","Thomson"],correct:"Bacquerel",questionId:"9"},{question:"The sun is a ____?",answers:["Star","Planet","Meteor","Asteroid"],correct:"Star",questionId:"10"},{question:"Which is the outermost in the solar system?",answers:["Neptune","Jupiter","Venus","Mars"],correct:"Neptune",questionId:"1"},{question:"Deficiency of Vitamin-D results in?",answers:["osteomalacia","scurvy","rickets","night blindness"],correct:"rickets",questionId:"2"},{question:"Which is easily visible from the Earth?",answers:["Neptune","Jupiter","Venus","Mars"],correct:"Venus",questionId:"23"},{question:"Which planet is closest to the Earth?",answers:["Mercury","Mars","Jupiter","Venus"],correct:"Mercury",questionId:"17"},{question:"Average adult blood volume in litres?",answers:["5","3","6","4"],correct:"5",questionId:"11"},{question:"Most abundant element in the universe?",answers:["Carbon Dioxide","Hydrogen","Oxygen","Silicon"],correct:"Hydrogen",questionId:"12"},{question:"Most abundant element in the Earth's crust?",answers:["Carbon Dioxide","Hydrogen","Oxygen","Silicon"],correct:"Oxygen",questionId:"13"},{question:"Which planet moves around the Sun with the highest speed?",answers:["Mercury","Saturn","Jupiter","Mars"],correct:"Mercury",questionId:"18"},{question:"Which planet is closest to the Earth?",answers:["Mercury","Mars","Jupiter","Venus"],correct:"Mercury",questionId:"17"},{question:"Which planet is referred to as Earth's bodyguard?",answers:["Mercury","Mars","Jupiter","Venus"],correct:"Jupiter",questionId:"25"},{question:"Planets visible from earth without telescope?",answers:["5","3","4","6"],correct:"5",questionId:"26"},{question:"SI unit of electric current?",answers:["Coulomb","Ohm","Volt","Ampere"],correct:"Ampere",questionId:"27"},{question:"Most abundant element in the Earth's crust?",answers:["Carbon Dioxide","Nitrogen","Oxygen","Silicon"],correct:"Nitrogen",questionId:"28"},{question:"What is Dry Ice?",answers:["Solid Carbon Dioxide","Solid Nitrogen","Solid Oxygen","Solid Hydrogen"],correct:"Solid Carbon Dioxide",questionId:"29"},{question:"Where is digestion completed?",answers:["Liver","Kidneys","Lungs","Large intestine"],correct:"Large intestine",questionId:"30"}],w=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return Promise.resolve(q.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},m=t(2),g=function(e){var s=e.score,t=e.playAgain;return Object(m.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-board",children:[Object(m.jsxs)("div",{className:"score",children:["You scored ",s," / 5 correct answers!"]}),Object(m.jsx)("button",{className:"playBtn",onClick:t,children:"Play Again"})]})},y=t(15),f=t(54),I=t(57),p=t(58),b=Object(f.a)({bar:Object(y.a)({paddingTop:"1.15rem",backgroundColor:"#fff"},"@media (max-width:780px)",{flexDirection:"column"}),menuItem:Object(y.a)({cursor:"pointer",flexGrow:1,"&:hover":{color:"#28c75d"}},"@media (max-width:780px)",{paddingBottom:"1rem"})});var v=function(e){var s=e.general,t=e.science,n=b();return Object(m.jsxs)(I.a,{position:"sticky",color:"rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.87)",className:n.bar,children:[Object(m.jsx)(p.a,{variant:"h6",className:n.menuItem,onClick:function(e){s("general")},children:"General Knowledge"}),Object(m.jsx)(p.a,{variant:"h6",className:n.menuItem,onClick:function(){t("science")},children:"Science"})]})},S=t(27),O=function(e){var s=e.question,t=e.options,n=e.selected,o=Object(a.useState)(t),r=Object(S.a)(o,2),i=r[0],c=r[1];return Object(m.jsxs)("div",{className:"questionBox",children:[Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"question",children:s}),i.map((function(e,s){return Object(m.jsx)("button",{className:"option",onClick:function(){c([e]),n(e)},children:e},s)}))]})},W=function(e){Object(r.a)(t,e);var s=Object(i.a)(t);function t(){var e;Object(n.a)(this,t);for(var o=arguments.length,r=new Array(o),i=0;i<o;i++)r[i]=arguments[i];return(e=s.call.apply(s,[this].concat(r))).state={questionBank:[],score:0,responses:0,currentQuiz:""},e.getQuestions=function(s){"general"===s?h().then((function(t){e.setState({questionBank:t,score:0,responses:0,currentQuiz:s})})):"science"===s?w().then((function(t){e.setState({questionBank:t,score:0,responses:0,currentQuiz:s})})):h().then((function(s){e.setState({questionBank:s})}))},e.computeAnswer=function(s,t){s===t&&e.setState({score:e.state.score+1}),e.setState({responses:e.state.responses<5?e.state.responses+1:5})},e.playAgain=function(){e.getQuestions(e.state.currentQuiz),e.setState({score:0,responses:0})},e}return Object(o.a)(t,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.getQuestions()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return Object(m.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(m.jsx)(v,{general:function(s){return e.getQuestions(s)},science:function(s){return e.getQuestions(s)}}),Object(m.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"title",children:"Quizbee"}),this.state.questionBank.length>0&&this.state.responses<=5&&this.state.questionBank.map((function(s){var t=s.question,n=s.answers,o=s.correct,r=s.questionId;return Object(m.jsx)(O,{question:t,options:n,selected:function(s){return e.computeAnswer(s,o)}},r)}))]}),Object(m.jsx)("div",{children:5===this.state.responses?Object(m.jsx)(g,{score:this.state.score,playAgain:this.playAgain}):null})]})}}]),t}(c.a.Component);d.a.render(Object(m.jsx)(W,{}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[41,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.7cb802a1.chunk.js.map